shopcj.com 2018-06-27

# Online Shopping in India - Shop @ Lowest Price at Shopcj for Mobiles, Pack of Sarees, hot deals, top picks, Bedsheet

### Privacy Policy:

The personally identifying information that You provide SCN with, for registering Yourself for availing of various services are no more than what would be required by SCN for administrative and management purposes for providing You with efficient and effective services and experience.

SCN respects every individual’s right to privacy and so is committed to protect your privacy. SCN agrees to take every reasonable and due care for keeping such information of yours in strict confidentiality and to use them only for the purposes and in furtherance thereof for which the same has been disclosed by You and for legitimate business purposes. SCN shall not release such information to any outside organizations, except to organization(s) which is a sponsor of the event/service for which such information has been collected. SCN shall be entitled to release the requisite personal information for the provision of services to its third party email service provider for the purposes of sending emails confirming registration, purchases, payments etc. However, SCN reserves the right to disclose such information if and when required by any Court Order or a subpoena or in response to a Law Enforcement and Regulatory Agency’s request.

### Personal & Non-Commercial Use:

  * 1 The right to use this SCN website is personal to You and is not transferable to any other person or entity. Each registration is for a single user only. We do not permit you to share your user name and password with any other person nor with multiple users on a network. Furthermore, You shall use this SCN website and services & materials therein strictly for non-commercial purposes only [and not indulge in any business activities]. 

### Personal & Non-Commercial Use:

  * 1 You may post reviews, comments, and other content and submit suggestions, ideas, comments, questions or other information, wherever required or permitted, apart from the information you provide to us or SCN Franchisee in the registration and Order Tracking process. "Your Information" is defined to include any information you provide to us or SCN Franchisee in the registration and Order Tracking process, in the feedback area or through any e-mail feature. Solely to enable SCN to use the information you supply us with, so that we are not violating any rights you might have in Your Information, you hereby agree to grant us a non-exclusive, worldwide, perpetual, irrevocable, royalty-free, sub-licensable right to exercise the copyright, publicity, and database rights (but no other rights) you have in Your Information, in any media now or in future known, with respect to Your Information. SCN will only use Your Information in accordance with this User Agreement. 
  * 2 You represent and warrant that you own or otherwise control all of the rights to the content that you post; that the content is accurate; that use of the content you supply does not violate this policy, rules and regulations and will not cause injury to any person or entity; and that you will indemnify SCN or its shareholders, affiliates and partners for all claims resulting from content you post or supply to SCN. SCN has the right but not the obligation to monitor and edit or remove any activity or content. SCN takes no responsibility and assumes no liability for any content posted by you or any third party. It is once again clarified that other than personally identifiable information, which is covered under the Privacy Policy any material you transmit or post to this SCN website will be considered non-confidential and non-proprietary. We will have no obligations with respect to such material.
  * 3 You are solely responsible for Your Information and Your Information:
  * a) shall not be false, inaccurate or misleading;
  * b) shall not be fraudulent;
  * c) shall not infringe any third party's intellectual property, trade secret or other proprietary rights or rights of publicity or privacy;
  * d) shall not be defamatory, libellous, unlawfully threatening or unlawfully harassing;
  * e) shall not be indecent, obscene or contain pornography or contain an "indecent representation of women" within the meaning of the Indecent Representation of Women (Prohibition) Act, 1986;
  * f) seditious, offensive, abusive, liable to incite racial or religious hatred, discriminatory, menacing, scandalous, inflammatory, blasphemous, in breach of confidence, in breach of privacy or which may cause annoyance or inconvenience;
  * g) which constitutes or encourages conduct that would be considered a criminal offence, give rise to civil liability, or otherwise be contrary to the law; or
  * h) shall not be or include material that is technically harmful (including, without limitation, computer viruses, logic bombs, Trojan horses, worms, harmful components, corrupted data or other malicious software or harmful data) or other computer programming routines that may damage, detrimentally interfere with, diminish value of, surreptitiously intercept or expropriate any system, data or personal information;
  * i) shall not create liability for us or cause us to lose (in whole or in part) the services of our ISPs or other suppliers; and
  * j) that is in the nature of political campaigning, commercial solicitation, chain letters, mass mailings or any form of ‘spam’;
  * k) that is illegal in any other way
  * SCN reserves the right (but not the obligation) to remove or edit such content but does not regularly review posted content.
  * 4 You shall abide by all the notices and all the terms and conditions (updated from time to time) contained and mentioned herein this Agreement, in good faith and with due diligence and care.
  * 5 You shall not use this SCN website, services and/or materials therein for any purpose that is unlawful or prohibited by these Terms, Conditions and Notices. You shall not use this SCN website, services and/or materials therein in any manner which could damage, disable, overburden and/or impair this SCN website or any services therein or the network(s) connected to this SCN website and interfere with other User’s use and enjoyment of this SCN website and/or services therein.
  * 6 You shall not attempt to gain unauthorized access to any service on this SCN website, other Users’ Account, Computer systems or networks connected to this SCN website through hacking, password mining or any other means. You shall not obtain or attempt to obtain any materials or information through any means not intentionally made available to You through this SCN website.
  * 7 We will fully co-operate with any law enforcement authorities or court order requesting or directing us to disclose the identity or locate anyone posting any material in breach of clauses 6.4 or 6.5 or elsewhere. Please be aware that even if you do not give SCN your real name, your Web browser transmits a unique address to us, which can be used by law enforcement officials to identify you.
  * 8 Certain elements of this SCN website will contain material submitted by other Users. SCN accepts no responsibility for the content, accuracy, conformity to applicable laws of such material. Part of this SCN website contains advertising/other material submitted to SCN by third parties. Responsibility for ensuring that material submitted for inclusion on this SCN website complies with applicable laws is exclusively on the advertisers and SCN will not be responsible for any claim, error, omission or inaccuracy in advertising material. SCN reserves the right to omit, suspend or change the position of any advertising material submitted for insertion. Acceptance of advertisements on this SCN website will be subject to SCN terms and conditions which are available on request. 

User Material and Conduct:
